<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Soulfilmgames on RadioBed</title>
    <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/soulfilmgame/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Soulfilmgames on RadioBed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</webMaster>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{oh-19}, All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/soulfilmgame/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Defintions</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/soulfilmgame/definitions/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/soulfilmgame/definitions/</guid>
        <description>Outline
Photo finish:
- The film does not necessarily die when the body does
- However, it is possible for the film to pass on
-&amp;ndash;
Motivation
Conscious beings that want chose to live as humans in order to better understand their nature; how they think, how they feel and how they perceive.
These beings have a tradition of playing the role of observing.
History
Common names for these beings:</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Scanner Memory Tokens</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/soulfilmgame/scannermemorytokens/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/soulfilmgame/scannermemorytokens/</guid>
        <description>Tokennized Scanner Memories My Scanners have been with me over three decades. How often do you sit back and revisit &amp;lsquo;The Goodtimes&amp;rsquo;. What value do you get from being able to reference critical decisions in life or defining a projects roadmap.
Tokens could access a particular memory on the network. For those with multiple scanners you could view a memory from multiple angles.
Those Special Moments Imagine being able to sit back and revisit any moment you wanted at the drop of a coin.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>&#39;Call Me T.V.&#39; - _Christopher_</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/soulfilmgame/callmetv/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/soulfilmgame/callmetv/</guid>
        <description>Late last night I saw something emerging from the television set background. Seeing faces is not such a crazy thing anymore. It has been about 9 months now that I have been haunted.
In come Spirit Film, Scanners, and now I am sitting infront of a TV set that seems to be studying me. No longer paying attention to the news I walk up to face the being and call it out.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Soul Film Tokens</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/soulfilmgame/outline/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/soulfilmgame/outline/</guid>
        <description>Since the enormous value expected from the upgrade to mind reading, Mine Radio and The Manifesto turned into an attempt on my life and outlasting conspiracy against my life, I have decided to take another go at the whole &amp;ldquo;Revolutionze The Modern World&amp;rdquo; thing.
Anyone who knows Palaver or logs into his room for Story Time knows about Soul Film, the Scanners, Mites, and other magical ferry-like creatures.
As the creator I feel a responsibility to our conscious beings to layout what it is to be here.</description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>