<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ET on RadioBed</title>
    <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/tags/et/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ET on RadioBed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</webMaster>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{oh-19}, All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/tags/et/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>The Threat</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/threat/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/threat/</guid>
        <description>Prepost idea on why it is I would feel such hate when it is illogical.
Threat How: Cause an earthquake that you want to look like I started. With the larger public fearing me, my kind would be immediately under a scope.
This lens could attenuate their capacity as well as threaten their super hero existence.
With these powerful and caring individuals removed from the equation, what is it they are really going after?</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Messenger</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/themessenger/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/themessenger/</guid>
        <description>Late December I was working on this site and uploaded this photo. The picture spoke to me and I received a message. I assumed the message was meant to reach me in June because that is when the photo was taken. About the same time, Stephanie went to Morea and came home with electric teeth. Just over a year ago while I was in New Zealand Stephanie went to Morea and took a photo.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Radio War Gear</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/notes/amazon/radio-war-gear/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/notes/amazon/radio-war-gear/</guid>
        <description>Let me clearly start this with:
I never endorse an aggressive response to an encounter with conscious beings - particularly those from a different place or time.
 One does not simply traverse the cosmic space-ways or tackle the metaphysics of phasing between timelines to arrive and start blasting radiation at the new individuals they find inhabiting this foreign time-scape.
A green color for those looking for lower frequency.</description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>