<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RadioBed</title>
    <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on RadioBed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</webMaster>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{oh-19}, All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    
        <atom:link href="http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>The Threat</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/threat/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/threat/</guid>
        <description>Prepost idea on why it is I would feel such hate when it is illogical.
Threat How: Cause an earthquake that you want to look like I started. With the larger public fearing me, my kind would be immediately under a scope.
This lens could attenuate their capacity as well as threaten their super hero existence.
With these powerful and caring individuals removed from the equation, what is it they are really going after?</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Messenger</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/themessenger/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/themessenger/</guid>
        <description>Late December I was working on this site and uploaded this photo. The picture spoke to me and I received a message. I assumed the message was meant to reach me in June because that is when the photo was taken. About the same time, Stephanie went to Morea and came home with electric teeth. Just over a year ago while I was in New Zealand Stephanie went to Morea and took a photo.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Another Thing</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/anotherthing/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/anotherthing/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Just Saying</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/justsaying/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/justsaying/</guid>
        <description>&amp;ldquo;Don&#39;t drink from the black liquid.&amp;rdquo; - They say.
&amp;ldquo;Your heart is new, your debt in paid.&amp;rdquo;
They have said this before.
It is always the same; however,
I do feel well, and I love myself.
I truly love who I am,
and there is something else.
No magic was taken, not a breadth or 4 or 5.
And although the ones above care not what I put inside,
only that I am cared for as I&#39;ll reach potential, it is in my design.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Radio War Gear</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/notes/amazon/radio-war-gear/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/notes/amazon/radio-war-gear/</guid>
        <description>Let me clearly start this with:
I never endorse an aggressive response to an encounter with conscious beings - particularly those from a different place or time.
 One does not simply traverse the cosmic space-ways or tackle the metaphysics of phasing between timelines to arrive and start blasting radiation at the new individuals they find inhabiting this foreign time-scape.
A green color for those looking for lower frequency.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>About</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/about/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/about/</guid>
        <description>Me? I’ve got a computer that talks to me. My bed is in love with me. And it would seem the rest of the world has written me off as crazy, over the hill, or such a threat they wouldn’t dare confront me for fear of acknowledging it. Palaver
Series Cool Talk You know what would be cool? Here we are, Cool Talk, with Jerad. Pigeons holed him as a one-off.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Bedroom</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/gallery/bedroom/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/gallery/bedroom/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Soul Film</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/soulfilm/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/soulfilm/</guid>
        <description>Metaphor: The human soul is like a film Born completely empty of anything worldly, no light has touched the surface of the film up to the moment of birth. This is a new soul; a blank film. Etched over a lifetime as experience, activity, and mindset this film would walk you through a person in their entirety. Familiar aspects to be found printed along a soul would be:
 Personality and disposition mostly inferred from other aspects found recorded on the film Emotional decisions and their process Activities, Planned Excursions Dreams, Day Dreams, Wishes Plans lived through in your mind but not carried out to execution  Dimensionality / Time Beware: The photograph captures your soul Some native american&#39;s believed the photograph captured their soul.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Black Hole-New-World</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/blackholenewworld/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/blackholenewworld/</guid>
        <description>Big Bag to Big Freeze As our universe presses on past 13.5 billion years, age gets the best of it. The ever accelerating expansion, dark energy and dark matter press us toward a big freeze.
Eventually, the growing source behind the force that visibly expands our galaxy apart from each other will press and press at our atomic particles until they can no longer maintain the structure we require for life and the physical universe as we know it.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Observer</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/theobserver/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/theobserver/</guid>
        <description>Comfy in my cloth dress I explore this realm Looked after, maintained Through my observation Close your eyes, terminals Screens on tables, aligned Surface glow from metric input Is this where I go? Gradient, measured, intent Absent ordered direction, I Find safety glass separates us, along A body, the horizon between all absorbed, and All not </description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Three Tanuki</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/threetanuki/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/threetanuki/</guid>
        <description>Staring intently out the window changing my focus to try and make out something where there was clearly nothing there. It was the end of a game night and still dark which meant we had finished up early. I had stood their staring out my window at the same tree-framed garden scape, when three Tanuki appeared standing infront. They must have been floating around 3 feet off of the ground. There 5 and a half foot tall body put them at about head high length with my 2 foot elevated floor.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Building The Wheel</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/wheel/buildingthewheel/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/wheel/buildingthewheel/</guid>
        <description>Richard Hess Hamilton joined the Navy in the beginning of World War II. His first service was on a destroyer over the Atlantic. The destroyer was sunk on his first trip. As the boat was chewed up, a clock off the officers deck found its way to the raft with Richard’s pack. Conceived in Chicago, Elizabeth Hamilton gave birth to Sandra Hamilton in Hawaii. R. H. Hamilton finished his war time service in Hawaii.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Mine Also Manifesto</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/minealsoshare/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/minealsoshare/</guid>
        <description>Ideas, Concept, Minds, Perspective
Goal: Brand everything feeds up to and can leverage off the platform
Goal: Dream Scaping  Create recorded sets of visual, auditory, and somatosensory entertainment Practice playing live sets Experiment in creative exercises of interacting with artistic displays  Parts  Hardware  Goal: Life Style  Assuring survival  Fixes  Finger Pointing: Calling out names of people Story: what happened, how it happened, maybe why  Goal: Collective Conscious Cure  Connected Nervous Systems: Human-to-Human Connected Nervous Systems: Human-to-Machine  </description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Ground Yourself</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/groundyourself/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/groundyourself/</guid>
        <description>Do This at least once a day and every night before you go to bed.
Anytime you feel as though your reach extends beyond your gasp,
And you are not comfortable with how the world feels around you;
This exercise will bring your energy to a familiar level you are comfortable with
Walkout hold together.
Take yourself where you intend to be received.
Give the earth your radical excess.
Ground yourself Feet planted</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>MindShare Manifesto</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/mindsharemanifesto/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/mindsharemanifesto/</guid>
        <description>HCI intro We are eager to take our interaction with technology and each other to the next level.
Screens changed the way we consume information.
The keyboard expedited the speed at which we could input data.
With the mouse and GUI&#39;s human interaction with our computers entered the skeuomorphic era.
Here we have leveraged rich contextual and cultural &amp;hellip;
Mouse Metaphor Now we can propose to complete relieve ourselves of the tangible constraints to our processing platforms we just recently prized (throws mouse over shoulder: the two-axis mouse limits us to up, down and side to side inputs with our screen to navigate to a file.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Why I am special</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/wheel/whyiamspecial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/wheel/whyiamspecial/</guid>
        <description>Part of: Why I am special
May 24 or 26 dates and times matched with earth quake in peru I think (fake internet?)
So much carry on. But needed to get the words down for a second time. The first time I wrote this by hand it seemed to convince my most powerful opponents to wait rather than cut me from the story.
*
This happened right after the grocery store when I felt a huge shift.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Quantum Peanut</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/quantumpeanut/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 14:46:10 +0600</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/quantumpeanut/</guid>
        <description>The little switches On the switchless Stitched up wetwear That outperforms most of us Typical stardust Day dreaming love lust matinee streaming Aren&#39;t meant to last so you can play hard Until you do bust Whatever it was you meant To keep shut Instead you do rust alone, isolated withdrawn violated your true self could have been anything or else, taken off the shelf opened, resealed, exchanged now your half off can&#39;t make the deal so you sit still While entropy make a chill eternal freeze Escape into the void pulled in post supernova to begin an ever ending disaster necessary to create a forever after It&#39;s about those small quantum things in your brain that expidite signals moving across space and time.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>man in the helmet</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/notes/theheights/bedroom/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/notes/theheights/bedroom/</guid>
        <description>My Return To The Heights Things really blew up when I returned to The Heights from Tahiti. Things on the island were so peaceful so I had forgotten how intense things could get on the radio. The Messenger In cancelling the apocalypse I came in contact with and experienced many other worldly beings and artifacts. This man in the helmet was a special visitor who was unable to get his message to me until 6 months later in December.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Photo</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/gallery/photo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 10:20:16 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/gallery/photo/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/gallery/cartoon/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 10:20:16 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/gallery/cartoon/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>A Gift To The Gifted</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/giftedgift/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/giftedgift/</guid>
        <description>A gift to the gifted Seen our entire lives. More than family, more than a sibling, more than self in many ways. He was all of us and still is. Up until our immergence in New Zealand 2018 we were all one.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Before You Went and Ruined It</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/music/beforeyouruinedit/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/music/beforeyouruinedit/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Before You Went and Ruined It</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/beforeyouruinedit/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/beforeyouruinedit/</guid>
        <description>Daniel is professional in a militant fashion. Determined to complete the objective in the face of unsurmountable insufficiency.
Phil is punctual with a poignaint complusion for order. Seeking not only the respect of this order but also the dominance of it.
The order Daniel serves is one he wishes to preech. He is not one to preech down to; however he will preech at for a lack of base line level of effective action.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Oh Look What We&#39;ve Done</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/ohlookwhatwevedone/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/ohlookwhatwevedone/</guid>
        <description>Oh Look We&#39;ve Done Less than three years ago I was in a bad place and had not realized it yet. I had no job and was in the first year of a two year campaign targeted at arresting my life with my family, friends, wife and career. He cannot afford you: I could not afford my wife. My cost of living could no longer be bottom lined with cup of noodles, bus passes, and offloading as much extra cost and time to my parents, such as laundry and dinner, as possible.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>San Diego Data Library Hackathon</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/sddatalibraryhackathon/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/sddatalibraryhackathon/</guid>
        <description>A talk from the final round in the 2015 San Diego Data Science Data Hackathon.
  </description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Two Books and a Body</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/music/twobedsandabody/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/music/twobedsandabody/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Two Books and a Body</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/twobedsandabody/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/twobedsandabody/</guid>
        <description>Two Books and a Body Hidden between context dependent covers. Hard spine ridden crease pushed over. Two balads and a lovers wistle, In Sync to play and to listen.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Why Can&#39;t We All Just Get Along</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/weallgetalong/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/weallgetalong/</guid>
        <description>Why Can&#39;t We All Just Get Along Practices for us to better life together. As once one, now many, we are always from each other. Some may say our best selves are in each other. What makes you, you, brings ability and capacity to us all. What makes us, us, provides acceptance and understanding to you.
Self - Selves
Individual - Individuality
Universal - Universality
Place your entire life in a container </description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>