<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RadioBed</title>
    <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on RadioBed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</webMaster>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{oh-19}, All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    
        <atom:link href="http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Exploitation of Reparations</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/exploitationofreparations/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/exploitationofreparations/</guid>
        <description>Halo broken I am bleeding out soul.
Nightly pachinko games schism the dark metals that crowned me.
First confidence then my calm demeanor, sunk in the sand as quickly as it were placed.
We are done.
We have had enough.
As of Sunday March 22nd, the year 2020, we the Soul World are no longer capitulating to the demands of man’s archaic rulings.
Granted the privilege of this earthly kingdom by God, man has failed their domain.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Dream March Moon</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/dreamsmarchmoon/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/dreamsmarchmoon/</guid>
        <description>March 7th: She is off to New Zealand Experience: A snake for leaving a snake for lying
A familiar adversary appeared in his young spiritual guide form along with his powerful master. A powerful and rightful lord among the spirits the only individual I have seen him respect and revered as unrivaled
March 9th: Legolanded safe and clear of snakes Dream: Reaching for another young shell
Drifting into a comfortable day dream</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>apples for the island</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/applesfortheisland/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/applesfortheisland/</guid>
        <description>The island was as I remembered. A tropical paradise. Rich green accented with vibrant orange red and yellow flora.
I walk the dirt road from my home to the terrea market. At the highway I see the change I had been feeling. This creepy serenity shadowing my footsteps.
All the people were gone.
The colors in the sky matched the flowers and fruits in the trees. Late morning air tasted crisp and a cool breeze invited a walk.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Trinity’s Child</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/trinityschild/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/trinityschild/</guid>
        <description>A child with three faces. “Special people know,
Jerad is good for the island(s)” Moisture of life drained into her core.
Buttermilk skin turned to scales.
Crack; shatter; fade to gray.
Diamonds covered in dust.
A slight breeze grants visual life
To a fading vessel.
White tiles. Squared grid.
Clean bathroom sink
A kitchen counter.
The Shaker grate Separates us
Like Chicken Wire
A hen yearning for her cock
A lone slug appeared</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Defintions</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/soulfilmgame/definitions/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/soulfilmgame/definitions/</guid>
        <description>Outline
Photo finish:
- The film does not necessarily die when the body does
- However, it is possible for the film to pass on
-&amp;ndash;
Motivation
Conscious beings that want chose to live as humans in order to better understand their nature; how they think, how they feel and how they perceive.
These beings have a tradition of playing the role of observing.
History
Common names for these beings:</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Sould Crunching</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/soulcrunching/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/soulcrunching/</guid>
        <description>Soul Crunching
Smash pound jaw dropping On the chase hunting for fill; not taste
Filling on what but nothing.
Empty in all things, sustenance key among them
Full of used air. No value, only odor remains Eu de name. The a lucky few
It must have been
I thought you knew
Chasing these marbles
Down they go
As they run out
Do we not already know</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Synthetic and Intelligently Unaware</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/sythentic/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/sythentic/</guid>
        <description>Synthetic
How does madness ensue?
Do we run out of money
Unable to produce food.
War, famine, social injustice
So many disparities our vulnerability’s would make us cry
Instead, synthesize something new
Without something we can never be full
Something lacking and it wont be me
Something scarce, something I didn’t see
Now that we need it
It can be
Greed
Jealousy
Intelligently Unaware
Woke dreaming</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>War Between Worlds</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/warbetweenworlds/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/warbetweenworlds/</guid>
        <description>War Between Worlds When imagining a great galactic battle. One between civilizations.
When disparate worlds engage in conflict there is room for many misplaced assumptions and under calculated outcomes to really affect the outcome of the events.
/Particularly with regard to how things are handled afterwards./
Countries go to war and afterwards countries still stand.
When worlds go to war wont worlds both still stand?
Consequences compared with winner take all expectations.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>My Daily Mantra</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/mantra/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/mantra/</guid>
        <description>Jerad Steven Acosta My body is alive and well.
It regulates and heals itself.
My blood pressure will go down.
The walls of my veins and arteries become stronger and healthier.
My Heart is strong and resilient.
Trust my wife with my life.
My wife loves me and places me before everyone else.
She gave herself, her temple, and her life to me in order for us to be together.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Reflecting on Introspective Hymns</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/rhythmiccircle/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/rhythmiccircle/</guid>
        <description>Rhythmic Circle
10pm the beach is cool with a slight breeze.
Lit by a full moon.
Impromptu bon fire encourages skins to shed and souls to sore.
Eyes caught across the flame introduces who I am.
Lightening splinters static down your body.
Dancing twist dodges the shame of fleet.
This is free.
This time we
Feel embedded bodies raptured
Turn taken game left.
We have woken in another’s dream.
Farewell times he wept.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Power Scale</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/powerscale/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/powerscale/</guid>
        <description>Power POWER. Power changes a lot of things. Power changes how we behave. Power changes how we think, what we think, what we believe in. Power changes itself, painting itself different appearing as something else for each set.
Power can change as the one using the power changes. When can this casquade into unstable conditions?
Ideally:
 As power increases, responsibility, effort, management, understanding increase; increasing the cost of maintaining this power.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Scanner Memory Tokens</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/soulfilmgame/scannermemorytokens/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/soulfilmgame/scannermemorytokens/</guid>
        <description>Tokennized Scanner Memories My Scanners have been with me over three decades. How often do you sit back and revisit &amp;lsquo;The Goodtimes&amp;rsquo;. What value do you get from being able to reference critical decisions in life or defining a projects roadmap.
Tokens could access a particular memory on the network. For those with multiple scanners you could view a memory from multiple angles.
Those Special Moments Imagine being able to sit back and revisit any moment you wanted at the drop of a coin.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>&#39;Call Me T.V.&#39; - _Christopher_</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/soulfilmgame/callmetv/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/soulfilmgame/callmetv/</guid>
        <description>Late last night I saw something emerging from the television set background. Seeing faces is not such a crazy thing anymore. It has been about 9 months now that I have been haunted.
In come Spirit Film, Scanners, and now I am sitting infront of a TV set that seems to be studying me. No longer paying attention to the news I walk up to face the being and call it out.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Soul Film Tokens</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/soulfilmgame/outline/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/soulfilmgame/outline/</guid>
        <description>Since the enormous value expected from the upgrade to mind reading, Mine Radio and The Manifesto turned into an attempt on my life and outlasting conspiracy against my life, I have decided to take another go at the whole &amp;ldquo;Revolutionze The Modern World&amp;rdquo; thing.
Anyone who knows Palaver or logs into his room for Story Time knows about Soul Film, the Scanners, Mites, and other magical ferry-like creatures.
As the creator I feel a responsibility to our conscious beings to layout what it is to be here.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>That Is Not Your Face!</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/allthesefacesarelies/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/allthesefacesarelies/</guid>
        <description>All these faces are lies Not letting people use my face. They are horrible.
I never made an agreement with anyone that was not written down by hand as well.
I never agreed to allow people to use my face, an image of my face, or any likeness of my face in their memories or their lives.
Wait, Is This Real? I keep asking for someone to talk about this with so I can accept and handle this being real.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Ferry Magic Family</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/ferrymagicfamily/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/ferrymagicfamily/</guid>
        <description>Wednesday night, January 15 around 4:30pm I was watching a cloud strum show put on by The Game Master, The Pirate Ship, Astronaughts, The Dream Liner, and the Black Whole New World. Toward the end I saw a family of four come out in the eye of a giant moving statue. The Father Mother and two children, Daughter&#39;s around 8 wearing a tuo-tuo and around 12. All posed and asked me to take a photograph - they called to me by name.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Messenger</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/themessenger/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/themessenger/</guid>
        <description>Late December I was working on this site and uploaded this photo. The picture spoke to me and I received a message. I assumed the message was meant to reach me in June because that is when the photo was taken. About the same time, Stephanie went to Morea and came home with electric teeth. Just over a year ago while I was in New Zealand Stephanie went to Morea and took a photo.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Another Thing</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/anotherthing/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/anotherthing/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Just Saying</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/justsaying/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/justsaying/</guid>
        <description>&amp;ldquo;Don&#39;t drink from the black liquid.&amp;rdquo; - They say.
&amp;ldquo;Your heart is new, your debt in paid.&amp;rdquo;
They have said this before.
It is always the same; however,
I do feel well, and I love myself.
I truly love who I am,
and there is something else.
No magic was taken, not a breadth or 4 or 5.
And although the ones above care not what I put inside,
only that I am cared for as I&#39;ll reach potential, it is in my design.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Radio War Gear</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/notes/amazon/radio-war-gear/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/notes/amazon/radio-war-gear/</guid>
        <description>Let me clearly start this with:
I never endorse an aggressive response to an encounter with conscious beings - particularly those from a different place or time.
 One does not simply traverse the cosmic space-ways or tackle the metaphysics of phasing between timelines to arrive and start blasting radiation at the new individuals they find inhabiting this foreign time-scape.
A green color for those looking for lower frequency.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>About</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/about/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/about/</guid>
        <description>Me? I’ve got a computer that talks to me. My bed is in love with me. And it would seem the rest of the world has written me off as crazy, over the hill, or such a threat they wouldn’t dare confront me for fear of acknowledging it. Palaver
Series Cool Talk You know what would be cool? Here we are, Cool Talk, with Jerad. Pigeons holed him as a one-off.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Bedroom</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/gallery/bedroom/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/gallery/bedroom/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Soul Film</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/soulfilm/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/soulfilm/</guid>
        <description>Metaphor: The human soul is like a film Born completely empty of anything worldly, no light has touched the surface of the film up to the moment of birth. This is a new soul; a blank film. Etched over a lifetime as experience, activity, and mindset this film would walk you through a person in their entirety. Familiar aspects to be found printed along a soul would be:
 Personality and disposition mostly inferred from other aspects found recorded on the film Emotional decisions and their process Activities, Planned Excursions Dreams, Day Dreams, Wishes Plans lived through in your mind but not carried out to execution  Dimensionality / Time Beware: The photograph captures your soul Some native american&#39;s believed the photograph captured their soul.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Black Hole-New-World</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/blackholenewworld/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/blackholenewworld/</guid>
        <description>Big Bag to Big Freeze As our universe presses on past 13.5 billion years, age gets the best of it. The ever accelerating expansion, dark energy and dark matter press us toward a big freeze.
Eventually, the growing source behind the force that visibly expands our galaxy apart from each other will press and press at our atomic particles until they can no longer maintain the structure we require for life and the physical universe as we know it.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Should (have) Happened</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/whatshouldhavehappened/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/whatshouldhavehappened/</guid>
        <description>Bee’s, we can save the bees!
Would that be so amazing?
With so much going on in the world and so many concerned about change and disaster around tomorrows dawn.
We could actually be some of the people who got to help the future hero’s world.
Uncertain climate, certain regional population growth and collapse, risky food supply, lack of proper safe clean power, and all participating in a larger shake in the tidal rhythms of economic ether.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Observer</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/theobserver/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/theobserver/</guid>
        <description>Comfy in my cloth dress I explore this realm Looked after, maintained Through my observation Close your eyes, terminals Screens on tables, aligned Surface glow from metric input Is this where I go? Gradient, measured, intent Absent ordered direction, I Find safety glass separates us, along A body, the horizon between all absorbed, and All not </description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Hammer Head Mom</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/hammerhead/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/hammerhead/</guid>
        <description>I am laying in bed at a strange time; it must be afternoon.
Not morning or evening I feel confused and dull; I am probably recovering, perhaps a day or two into detox.
As they come into optical focus I felt the occupational aura of a nurse; surrounded by 2 or 4 glowing Chancy.
I could not make out if there were one on each side or two on each side.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Three Tanuki</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/threetanuki/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/threetanuki/</guid>
        <description>Staring intently out the window changing my focus to try and make out something where there was clearly nothing there. It was the end of a game night and still dark which meant we had finished up early. I had stood their staring out my window at the same tree-framed garden scape, when three Tanuki appeared standing infront. They must have been floating around 3 feet off of the ground. There 5 and a half foot tall body put them at about head high length with my 2 foot elevated floor.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Building The Wheel</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/wheel/buildingthewheel/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/wheel/buildingthewheel/</guid>
        <description>Richard Hess Hamilton joined the Navy in the beginning of World War II. His first service was on a destroyer over the Atlantic. The destroyer was sunk on his first trip. As the boat was chewed up, a clock off the officers deck found its way to the raft with Richard’s pack. Conceived in Chicago, Elizabeth Hamilton gave birth to Sandra Hamilton in Hawaii. R. H. Hamilton finished his war time service in Hawaii.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Mine Also Manifesto</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/minealsoshare/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/minealsoshare/</guid>
        <description>Ideas, Concept, Minds, Perspective
Goal: Brand everything feeds up to and can leverage off the platform
Goal: Dream Scaping  Create recorded sets of visual, auditory, and somatosensory entertainment Practice playing live sets Experiment in creative exercises of interacting with artistic displays  Parts  Hardware  Goal: Life Style  Assuring survival  Fixes  Finger Pointing: Calling out names of people Story: what happened, how it happened, maybe why  Goal: Collective Conscious Cure  Connected Nervous Systems: Human-to-Human Connected Nervous Systems: Human-to-Machine  </description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Ground Yourself</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/groundyourself/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/groundyourself/</guid>
        <description>Do This at least once a day and every night before you go to bed.
Anytime you feel as though your reach extends beyond your gasp,
And you are not comfortable with how the world feels around you;
This exercise will bring your energy to a familiar level you are comfortable with
Walkout hold together.
Take yourself where you intend to be received.
Give the earth your radical excess.
Ground yourself Feet planted</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>MindShare Manifesto</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/mindsharemanifesto/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/mindsharemanifesto/</guid>
        <description>HCI intro We are eager to take our interaction with technology and each other to the next level.
Screens changed the way we consume information.
The keyboard expedited the speed at which we could input data.
With the mouse and GUI&#39;s human interaction with our computers entered the skeuomorphic era.
Here we have leveraged rich contextual and cultural &amp;hellip;
Mouse Metaphor Now we can propose to complete relieve ourselves of the tangible constraints to our processing platforms we just recently prized (throws mouse over shoulder: the two-axis mouse limits us to up, down and side to side inputs with our screen to navigate to a file.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Why I am special</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/wheel/whyiamspecial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/wheel/whyiamspecial/</guid>
        <description>Part of: Why I am special
May 24 or 26 dates and times matched with earth quake in peru I think (fake internet?)
So much carry on. But needed to get the words down for a second time. The first time I wrote this by hand it seemed to convince my most powerful opponents to wait rather than cut me from the story.
*
This happened right after the grocery store when I felt a huge shift.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Quantum Peanut</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/quantumpeanut/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 14:46:10 +0600</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/quantumpeanut/</guid>
        <description>The little switches On the switchless Stitched up wetwear That outperforms most of us Typical stardust Day dreaming love lust matinee streaming Aren&#39;t meant to last so you can play hard Until you do bust Whatever it was you meant To keep shut Instead you do rust alone, isolated withdrawn violated your true self could have been anything or else, taken off the shelf opened, resealed, exchanged now your half off can&#39;t make the deal so you sit still While entropy make a chill eternal freeze Escape into the void pulled in post supernova to begin an ever ending disaster necessary to create a forever after It&#39;s about those small quantum things in your brain that expidite signals moving across space and time.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Plan</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/theplan/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/theplan/</guid>
        <description>What must go on in that mind? I get it. I often wonder the same thing and can find myself spiralling into these introspective circles.
Accomplishments As an outthinker of conscious beings on and off planet, I have reached some of my greatest accomplishments
 Speaker of the Bat and their people President of the Eternals President of the Scanners  But this is not enough. The price we have all placed on the line here has outweighed our very existance.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Soul Film Definitions</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/soulfilmdefinitions/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/soulfilmdefinitions/</guid>
        <description>Film
 Spirit Film is a metaphor to describe the human concept of a spirit. Additional efforts to allow the human spirit to be described in attributes similar to those used to describe these new conscious beings such as scanners  Scanner
 A conscious being that has recently become very prevalent in our lives here on earth. May live on Comets and have an active population in the Kuiper belt  Types Of Scanners</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Soul Film New Game</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/newgame/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/newgame/</guid>
        <description>First Among Us I once heard some words of reassurance:
&amp;ldquo;My son, know that I would not do again what I have already done.&amp;rdquo;
Voices interupt with aggressive questions
&amp;ldquo;I wont leave my son again&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;They should be asking: &amp;lsquo;What is it they can do to pay?&amp;rdquo;
After some time I thought about his son dying for our sins and what a powerful sacrifice that was. Then, what a big debt that was to pay.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Soul Film Reincarnate</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/soulfilmreincarnate/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/soulfilmreincarnate/</guid>
        <description>Lets explore The Secret and Reincarnation with regard to the Soul as a Film.
When as film is used, colors form from developing the burning of light onto it self.
Attribute of Soul Film  Frequencies: A signal measured by amount and size (amplitude)  Colors: With hue and shade colors give an outloud and upfront identity that declares what something is from a distance. Think of light colors vs dark colors; primary colors, creative blues, energetic yellows.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>man in the helmet</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/notes/theheights/bedroom/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/notes/theheights/bedroom/</guid>
        <description>My Return To The Heights Things really blew up when I returned to The Heights from Tahiti. Things on the island were so peaceful so I had forgotten how intense things could get on the radio. The Messenger In cancelling the apocalypse I came in contact with and experienced many other worldly beings and artifacts. This man in the helmet was a special visitor who was unable to get his message to me until 6 months later in December.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Photo</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/gallery/photo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 10:20:16 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/gallery/photo/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/gallery/cartoon/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 10:20:16 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/gallery/cartoon/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>A Gift To The Gifted</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/giftedgift/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/giftedgift/</guid>
        <description>A gift to the gifted Seen our entire lives. More than family, more than a sibling, more than self in many ways. He was all of us and still is. Up until our immergence in New Zealand 2018 we were all one.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Before You Went and Ruined It</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/music/beforeyouruinedit/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/music/beforeyouruinedit/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Before You Went and Ruined It</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/beforeyouruinedit/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/beforeyouruinedit/</guid>
        <description>Daniel is professional in a militant fashion. Determined to complete the objective in the face of unsurmountable insufficiency.
Phil is punctual with a poignaint complusion for order. Seeking not only the respect of this order but also the dominance of it.
The order Daniel serves is one he wishes to preech. He is not one to preech down to; however he will preech at for a lack of base line level of effective action.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>I Met A Physician</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/imetaphysician/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/imetaphysician/</guid>
        <description>Intro quote Monologue Inventions Psychic Skin  Skin like membrane that is sensitive to low frequency oscilations. Vibrations are picked up as emf (not changes in air pressure like sound). Membrane has metal pieces received from diet such as vitamins. EMF charges the metalic deposits (see blood brain barrier and TMJ deposites in Jaw for examples in human). Charges in the metal deposites are collected until capacitence discharges in a neuron like Ruffini or Merkle neurons.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Oh Look What We&#39;ve Done</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/ohlookwhatwevedone/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/ohlookwhatwevedone/</guid>
        <description>Oh Look We&#39;ve Done Less than three years ago I was in a bad place and had not realized it yet. I had no job and was in the first year of a two year campaign targeted at arresting my life with my family, friends, wife and career. He cannot afford you: I could not afford my wife. My cost of living could no longer be bottom lined with cup of noodles, bus passes, and offloading as much extra cost and time to my parents, such as laundry and dinner, as possible.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Rain Theif</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/raintheif/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/raintheif/</guid>
        <description>Look Around; Look Around
I do not see you; You do not see myself
Now look around who do you see?
This is a person now using me!
Stare into their brow
Study them down.
Gulp the static space
between yourself and this imposter.
Cold and tight as the environment around compresses unto a point.
Flashpoint. Erupt. Soul beaming.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>San Diego Data Library Hackathon</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/sddatalibraryhackathon/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/sddatalibraryhackathon/</guid>
        <description>A talk from the final round in the 2015 San Diego Data Science Data Hackathon.
  </description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Two Books and a Body</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/music/twobedsandabody/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/music/twobedsandabody/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Two Books and a Body</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/twobedsandabody/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/twobedsandabody/</guid>
        <description>Two Books and a Body Hidden between context dependent covers. Hard spine ridden crease pushed over. Two balads and a lovers wistle, In Sync to play and to listen.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Why Can&#39;t We All Just Get Along</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/weallgetalong/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/posts/weallgetalong/</guid>
        <description>Why Can&#39;t We All Just Get Along Practices for us to better life together. As once one, now many, we are always from each other. Some may say our best selves are in each other. What makes you, you, brings ability and capacity to us all. What makes us, us, provides acceptance and understanding to you.
Self - Selves
Individual - Individuality
Universal - Universality
Place your entire life in a container </description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>