<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Storytimes on RadioBed</title>
    <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Storytimes on RadioBed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</webMaster>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{oh-19}, All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>apples for the island</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/applesfortheisland/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/applesfortheisland/</guid>
        <description>The island was as I remembered. A tropical paradise. Rich green accented with vibrant orange red and yellow flora.
I walk the dirt road from my home to the terrea market. At the highway I see the change I had been feeling. This creepy serenity shadowing my footsteps.
All the people were gone.
The colors in the sky matched the flowers and fruits in the trees. Late morning air tasted crisp and a cool breeze invited a walk.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Trinity’s Child</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/trinityschild/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/trinityschild/</guid>
        <description>A child with three faces. “Special people know,
Jerad is good for the island(s)” Moisture of life drained into her core.
Buttermilk skin turned to scales.
Crack; shatter; fade to gray.
Diamonds covered in dust.
A slight breeze grants visual life
To a fading vessel.
White tiles. Squared grid.
Clean bathroom sink
A kitchen counter.
The Shaker grate Separates us
Like Chicken Wire
A hen yearning for her cock
A lone slug appeared</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Sould Crunching</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/soulcrunching/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/soulcrunching/</guid>
        <description>Soul Crunching
Smash pound jaw dropping On the chase hunting for fill; not taste
Filling on what but nothing.
Empty in all things, sustenance key among them
Full of used air. No value, only odor remains Eu de name. The a lucky few
It must have been
I thought you knew
Chasing these marbles
Down they go
As they run out
Do we not already know</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Synthetic and Intelligently Unaware</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/sythentic/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/sythentic/</guid>
        <description>Synthetic
How does madness ensue?
Do we run out of money
Unable to produce food.
War, famine, social injustice
So many disparities our vulnerability’s would make us cry
Instead, synthesize something new
Without something we can never be full
Something lacking and it wont be me
Something scarce, something I didn’t see
Now that we need it
It can be
Greed
Jealousy
Intelligently Unaware
Woke dreaming</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Reflecting on Introspective Hymns</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/rhythmiccircle/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/rhythmiccircle/</guid>
        <description>Rhythmic Circle
10pm the beach is cool with a slight breeze.
Lit by a full moon.
Impromptu bon fire encourages skins to shed and souls to sore.
Eyes caught across the flame introduces who I am.
Lightening splinters static down your body.
Dancing twist dodges the shame of fleet.
This is free.
This time we
Feel embedded bodies raptured
Turn taken game left.
We have woken in another’s dream.
Farewell times he wept.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Soul Film</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/soulfilm/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/soulfilm/</guid>
        <description>Metaphor: The human soul is like a film Born completely empty of anything worldly, no light has touched the surface of the film up to the moment of birth. This is a new soul; a blank film. Etched over a lifetime as experience, activity, and mindset this film would walk you through a person in their entirety. Familiar aspects to be found printed along a soul would be:
 Personality and disposition mostly inferred from other aspects found recorded on the film Emotional decisions and their process Activities, Planned Excursions Dreams, Day Dreams, Wishes Plans lived through in your mind but not carried out to execution  Dimensionality / Time Beware: The photograph captures your soul Some native american&#39;s believed the photograph captured their soul.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Black Hole-New-World</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/blackholenewworld/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/blackholenewworld/</guid>
        <description>Big Bag to Big Freeze As our universe presses on past 13.5 billion years, age gets the best of it. The ever accelerating expansion, dark energy and dark matter press us toward a big freeze.
Eventually, the growing source behind the force that visibly expands our galaxy apart from each other will press and press at our atomic particles until they can no longer maintain the structure we require for life and the physical universe as we know it.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The Plan</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/theplan/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/theplan/</guid>
        <description>What must go on in that mind? I get it. I often wonder the same thing and can find myself spiralling into these introspective circles.
Accomplishments As an outthinker of conscious beings on and off planet, I have reached some of my greatest accomplishments
 Speaker of the Bat and their people President of the Eternals President of the Scanners  But this is not enough. The price we have all placed on the line here has outweighed our very existance.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Soul Film Definitions</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/soulfilmdefinitions/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/soulfilmdefinitions/</guid>
        <description>Film
 Spirit Film is a metaphor to describe the human concept of a spirit. Additional efforts to allow the human spirit to be described in attributes similar to those used to describe these new conscious beings such as scanners  Scanner
 A conscious being that has recently become very prevalent in our lives here on earth. May live on Comets and have an active population in the Kuiper belt  Types Of Scanners</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Soul Film New Game</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/newgame/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/newgame/</guid>
        <description>First Among Us I once heard some words of reassurance:
&amp;ldquo;My son, know that I would not do again what I have already done.&amp;rdquo;
Voices interupt with aggressive questions
&amp;ldquo;I wont leave my son again&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;They should be asking: &amp;lsquo;What is it they can do to pay?&amp;rdquo;
After some time I thought about his son dying for our sins and what a powerful sacrifice that was. Then, what a big debt that was to pay.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Soul Film Reincarnate</title>
        <link>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/soulfilmreincarnate/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://radiobed.jerad.xyz/en/storytime/soulfilmreincarnate/</guid>
        <description>Lets explore The Secret and Reincarnation with regard to the Soul as a Film.
When as film is used, colors form from developing the burning of light onto it self.
Attribute of Soul Film  Frequencies: A signal measured by amount and size (amplitude)  Colors: With hue and shade colors give an outloud and upfront identity that declares what something is from a distance. Think of light colors vs dark colors; primary colors, creative blues, energetic yellows.</description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>