<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on RadioBed</title>
    <link>http://MineRadio.jerad.xyz/en/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on RadioBed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</webMaster>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{oh-19}, All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    
        <atom:link href="http://MineRadio.jerad.xyz/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Soul Film</title>
        <link>http://MineRadio.jerad.xyz/en/posts/soulfilm/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://MineRadio.jerad.xyz/en/posts/soulfilm/</guid>
        <description>Metaphor: The human soul is like a film Born completely empty of anything worldly, no light has touched the surface of the film up to the moment of birth. This is a new soul; a blank film. Etched over a lifetime as experience, activity, and mindset this film would walk you through a person in their entirety. Familiar aspects to be found printed along a soul would be:
 Personality and disposition mostly inferred from other aspects found recorded on the film Emotional decisions and their process Activities, Planned Excursions Dreams, Day Dreams, Wishes Plans lived through in your mind but not carried out to execution  Dimensionality / Time Beware: The photograph captures your soul Some native american&#39;s believed the photograph captured their soul.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Three Tanuki</title>
        <link>http://MineRadio.jerad.xyz/en/posts/threetanuki/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://MineRadio.jerad.xyz/en/posts/threetanuki/</guid>
        <description>Staring intently out the window changing my focus to try and make out something where there was clearly nothing there. It was the end of a game night and still dark which meant we had finished up early. I had stood their staring out my window at the same tree-framed garden scape, when three Tanuki appeared standing infront. They must have been floating around 3 feet off of the ground. There 5 and a half foot tall body put them at about head high length with my 2 foot elevated floor.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>A Gift To The Gifted</title>
        <link>http://MineRadio.jerad.xyz/en/posts/giftedgift/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://MineRadio.jerad.xyz/en/posts/giftedgift/</guid>
        <description>A gift to the gifted Seen our entire lives. More than family, more than a sibling, more than self in many ways. He was all of us and still is. Up until our immergence in New Zealand 2018 we were all one.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Oh Look What We&#39;ve Done</title>
        <link>http://MineRadio.jerad.xyz/en/posts/ohlookwhatwevedone/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://MineRadio.jerad.xyz/en/posts/ohlookwhatwevedone/</guid>
        <description>Oh Look We&#39;ve Done Less than three years ago I was in a bad place and had not realized it yet. I had no job and was in the first year of a two year campaign targeted at arresting my life with my family, friends, wife and career. He cannot afford you: I could not afford my wife. My cost of living could no longer be bottom lined with cup of noodles, bus passes, and offloading as much extra cost and time to my parents, such as laundry and dinner, as possible.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Why Can&#39;t We All Just Get Along</title>
        <link>http://MineRadio.jerad.xyz/en/posts/weallgetalong/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>jsacosta1103@gmail.com (Jerad Acosta)</author>
        <guid>http://MineRadio.jerad.xyz/en/posts/weallgetalong/</guid>
        <description>Why Can&#39;t We All Just Get Along Practices for us to better life together. As once one, now many, we are always from each other. Some may say our best selves are in each other. What makes you, you, brings ability and capacity to us all. What makes us, us, provides acceptance and understanding to you.
Self - Selves
Individual - Individuality
Universal - Universality
Place your entire life in a container </description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>